

# Julia Mari Ong Oh

Scarborough, M1B 4K8

jojuliamari@gmail.com +6479170472

https://www.youtube.com/c/ohanajulia

https://instagram.com/cookieth.mnl

#### **PROFILE**

Female

September 14, 2003 (18 years old) Philippines Student Permit

Ready to serve and work with and for others; capable of learning and quickly inderstanding concepts, while applying critical thinking. Manages academics and other hobbies and work.

#### **SKILLS**

- Fluent in English
- Friendly and can easily communicate with others
- Excellent Time Management
- Strong endurance and athleticism
- Knowledgeable with technology and applications (Microsoft Word, Excel, social media, etc)
- Basing Digital Marketing Knowledge
- Intermediate Video Editing Skills
- Basic Photoshop Skills
- Basic Baking Skills

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### CASHIER/BARISTA/BAKER

## Coffee Time

Jan 2022 - Present

- Handling Cash and Taking Orders
- Baking and cooking muffins, pastries, and breakfasts
- Preparing food that will be used for sandwiches, bagels, etc.
- Brewing coffee, and making cold drinks
- Organizing and maintaining cleanliness in store

### SELF EMPLOYED BAKER

## Home Based Business

Aug 2020 - Sept 2021

- · Costing for ingredients and materials
- Community involvement: Participating in charity programs
- Created Public Materials to be posted on Social Media (Instagram and Facebook)
- Handle customers online
- Flexible hours(Night, weekends, and holidays)

## **EDUCATION HISTORY**

# Software Engineering Technician

January 2022-Present

# Centennial College

- First Year College Student

Science, Technology, Engineering, and Mathematics (K-12)

2019-2021

# Ateneo Senior High School

- Third Honors
- Member of Cheerdance Team
- Member of School Fair Promotions Committee

## **High School**

2008-2019

# **Assumption College San Lorenzo**

- Member of Dance Troupe
- Member of Math Enrichment Class
- Member of Finance Committee